Guide to the Royal College of Art Sketch Club Collection
Yale Center for British Art, Rare Books and Manuscripts
Royal College of Art Sketch Club Collection
1934-1937
MSS.54
Yale Center for British Art, Rare Books and Manuscripts
.42
1 box
The collection includes the correspondence of and with various secretaries of the Royal College of Art (RCA) Students' Group, or Sketch Club, and contains 79 letters and postcards and 11 draft letters, written between 1934 and 1937. The materials focus primarily on the group's annual exhibition, and discuss the facilities, invite prominent figures, and solicit donations and judges for special prizes. The letters' authors include, in addition to the groups' secretaries, several notable artistic and literary figures in 1930s England, such as Wyndham Lewis, Kenneth Clark, Vanessa Bell, Clive Bell, and John Gielglud.
Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club
Arnold, Elizabeth, 1939-
Ashton, Leigh, 1897-1983
Bell, Clive, 1881-1964
Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961
Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983
Clayton, Muriel
Courtauld, Samuel, 1876-1947
Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990
Dick, William Reid, 1879-1961
Dodgson, Campbell, 1867-1948
Evans, J. H.
Gardner, H. Vernon
Gielgud, John, 1904-2000
Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959
Hall, Evelyn F.
Hambleden, William Smith, Viscount, 1903-1948
Hardie, Martin, 1875-1952
Hughes, George Ravensworth
Kauffer, E. McKnight (Edward McKnight), 1890-1954
Korda, Alexander, Sir, 1893-1956
Laver, James, 1899-1975
Lawson, Vivien
Lewis, Wyndham, 1882-1957
Maclagan, Eric Robert Dalrymple, 1879-1951
Marlow, Reginald Herbert
Mitchison, Naomi, 1897-1999
Monck, Walter Nugent Bligh, 1878-1958
Mortimer, Raymond, 1895-1980
Nash, John, 1893-1977
Phillips, Fred P., 1880-
Pope, G. R.
Rackham, Bernard, 1876-1964
Raverat, Gwen, 1885-1957
Read, Herbert, 1893-1968
Robinson, Edward G., 1893-1973
Rothenstein, William, 1872-1945
Rutherston, Albert, 1881-1953
Schwabe, Randolph, 1885-1948
Simmonds, W. G. (William George), 1876-1968
Wellington, Hubert, 1879-
Wilenski, R. H. (Reginald Howard), 1887-1975
Willcock, J. P.
Biographical / Historical
The Government School of Design, predecessor to the Royal College of Art, was founded in 1837. Its goal, in its earliest years, was to train students in techniques vital to improving industrial and everyday products in England; this mission would evolve in various ways under ensuing directors, and per the demands of the students themselves. By 1896, when the school was renamed the Royal College of Art, the school had assimilated the influence of the Arts and Crafts Movement and embraced a broader vision of art and design.
During the first few decades of the twentieth century, new leadership brought ever more shifts in the mission of the RCA. The painter William Rothenstein became Principal in 1920 and began to shift the school's emphasis towards the study of fine art, and the training of designers, rather than teachers. In the words of sculptor Henry Moore: "he changed the college completely." In 1935, painter Percy Jowett succeeded Rothenstein as head of the RCA, continuing an approach more interested in the cultivation of new artistic styles and methods, rather than preserving traditional techniques. It was under the post-war reorganization of Robin Darwin, however, that the RCA fully embraced fine art and became a driving force in British post-war art.
During the 1930s, The Royal College of Art Students' Group, or Sketch Club, held annual exhibitions at the Victoria & Albert Museum, displaying students' work and awarding prizes for different genres and themes. The secretaries of the group included Frank B. Mason; J. Anthony Denney, later a fashion photographer for British Vogue; Margaret Kaye, an artist who worked in textiles and stained-glass; and Evelyn Hunt, a painter.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Yale Center for British Art, Friends of British Art.
Arrangement
The letters are arranged alphabetically, by the name of letter authors.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes 79 letters and postcards, and 11 draft letters, pertaining to the Royal College of Art Students' Group, or Sketch Club, written between 1934 and 1937. The letters concern the logistics of the group's annual exhibition, held at the Victoria & Albert Museum. The correspondence consists primarily of replies to solicitations written by secretaries of the RCA. In the replies, the authors--typically individuals involved in fine art, art and literary criticism, and museums--discuss their willingness to attend the show, or to sponsor and judge prizes for different categories of artistic production.
The letters offer insight into the various media used by students at the RCA and those valued by their correspondents, and into the continuing involvement of some of the figures with artistic education. Types of prizes mentioned include those in set design, theatrical costume, painting, embroidery, notebook sketches, posters, and ceramics. Some of the correspondents also express their enthusiasm for the RCA, such as painter and author Wyndham Lewis, while others express thoughts related to artistic practice, such as theater director Nugent Monck, who stresses the importance of responding to commissions. Most letters address the logistical details of funding and judging prizes.
Art, British -- 20th Century; Art, British -- Exhibitions -- 20th Century; Art -- Awards -- Great Britain; Art -- Competitions -- Great Britain; Art -- Study and teaching (Higher) -- Great Britain; Art schools -- Great Britain -- 20th Century; Art students -- Great Britain -- 20th Century; Costume -- Great Britain -- 20th Century; Drawing, British -- 20th Century; Embroidery -- Great Britain -- 20th Century; Painting, British -- 20th Century; Sculpture, British -- 20th Century; Theaters -- Stage-setting and scenery -- Great Britain -- 20th Century; Correspondence; Árnason, Barbara, 1911-1975 -- Correspondence; Arnold, Elizabeth, 1939- -- Correspondence; Ashton, Leigh, 1897-1983 -- Correspondence; Bawden, Edward, 1903-1989 -- Correspondence; Bell, Clive, 1881-1964 -- Correspondence; Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961 -- Correspondence; Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983 -- Correspondence; Clayton, Muriel -- Correspondence; Cohen, Dennis, 1891-1970 -- Correspondence; Courtauld, Samuel, 1876-1947 -- Correspondence; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Dick, William Reid, 1879-1961 -- Correspondence; Enthoven, Gabrielle, 1868-1950 -- Correspondence; Evans, J. H. -- Correspondence; Gardner, H. Vernon -- Correspondence; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000 -- Correspondence; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959 -- Correspondence; Hall, Evelyn F. -- Correspondence; Hambleden, William Smith, Viscount, 1903-1948 -- Correspondence; Hardie, Martin, 1875-1952 -- Correspondence; Hughes, George Ravensworth -- Correspondence; Hunt, Evelyn Janet, 1914-2001 -- Correspondence; Jago, Joseph -- Correspondence; John, Augustus, 1878-1961 -- Correspondence; Kauffer, E. McKnight (Edward McKnight), 1890-1954 -- Correspondence; Kaye, Margaret, 1912-2002 -- Correspondence; Korda, Alexander, Sir, 1893-1956 -- Correspondence; Laver, James, 1899-1975 -- Correspondence; Lawson, Vivien -- Correspondence; Lewis, Wyndham, 1882-1957 -- Correspondence; Maclagan, Eric Robert Dalrymple, 1879-1951 -- Correspondence; Marlow, Reginald Herbert -- Correspondence; Mason, Frank B. -- Correspondence; Mitchison, Naomi, 1897-1999 -- Correspondence; Monck, Walter Nugent Bligh, 1878-1958 -- Correspondence; Mortimer, Raymond, 1895-1980 -- Correspondence; Nash, John, 1893-1977 -- Correspondence; Phillips, Fred P., 1880- -- Correspondence; Pope, G. R. -- Correspondence; Rackham, Bernard, 1876-1964 -- Correspondence; Raverat, Gwen, 1885-1957 -- Correspondence; Ravilious, Eric William, 1903-1942 -- Correspondence; Read, Herbert, 1893-1968 -- Correspondence; Robinson, Edward G., 1893-1973 -- Correspondence; Rothenstein, William, 1872-1945 -- Correspondence; Rutherston, Albert, 1881-1953 -- Correspondence; Schwabe, Randolph, 1885-1948 -- Correspondence; Simmonds, W. G. (William George), 1876-1968 -- Correspondence; Wellington, Hubert, 1879- -- Correspondence; Wilenski, R. H. (Reginald Howard), 1887-1975 -- Correspondence; Willcock, J. P. -- Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Royal College of Art (Great Britain) -- Students -- Exhibitions; Victoria and Albert Museum
- Elizabeth Arnold letter to J. Anthony Denney, 1935 October 24; Arnold, Elizabeth, 1939-; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 23 x 18 cm (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Arnold, secretary to Kenneth Clark, asks about the ceremony time for the "Exhibition which Mr. Kenneth Clark is opening for the Royal College of Art Students' Group on November 16th."
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Arnold, Elizabeth, 1939- -- Correspondence; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983 -- Correspondence
- Leigh Ashton letter to Margaret Kaye, 1937 September 4; Ashton, Leigh, 1897-1983; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 24 x 19 cm (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Ashton requests information on the opening and closing dates of the "Royal College of Arts Students' exhibitions," for inclusion in the V&A Museum Handbill for November.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Ashton, Leigh, 1897-1983 -- Correspondence; Kaye, Margaret, 1912-2002 -- Correspondence; Victoria and Albert Museum
- Clive Bell letter to Evelyn Hunt, 1937?; Bell, Clive, 1881-1964; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 20 x 13 cm (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Bell responds to an apparent invitation to give a speech, noting: "A few not particularly well chosen paragraphs is the limit of my capacity. Will you let me know how you feel about it?" Bell includes a Parisian address where he may be reached for the next 10 days.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Bell, Clive, 1881-1964 -- Correspondence; Hunt, Evelyn Janet, 1914-2001 -- Correspondence
- Vanessa Bell letter to Frank B. Mason, 1934 October 9; Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 23 x 18 cm (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Bell accepts the invitation to "adjudicate some of the students' work" and inquires about dates.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961 -- Correspondence; Mason, Frank B. -- Correspondence
- Vanessa Bell letter to Evelyn Hunt, 1937 November 16; Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 23 x 18 cm (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Bell apologizes for the delay in answering a previous letter, on account of illness, and references an enclosed check to be used as a prize.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Bell, Vanessa, 1879-1961 -- Correspondence; Hunt, Evelyn Janet, 1914-2001 -- Correspondence
- Kenneth Clark letter to J. Anthony Denney, 1935 November 13; Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 24 x 19 cm (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Clark asks Denney if he might attend an exhibition prior to its opening. He also notes his name is misspelled on the invitation cards, "which does not matter except that it confuses people."
  General
  Letterhead: "National Gallery. Trafalgar Square."
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983 -- Correspondence; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence
- Muriel Clayton letter to Evelyn Hunt, 1937 November 28; Clayton, Muriel; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 18 x 13 cm (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Clayton apologizes for delay due to a holiday in Italy, and notes her desire for the prize to be an "annual affair." She expresses a wish for it to be for embroidery.
  Letterhead: "31 Courtfield Road S.W.7 Frobisher 1671"
  Correspondence; Embroidery; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Clayton, Muriel -- Correspondence; Hunt, Evelyn Janet, 1914-2001 -- Correspondence
- Samuel Courtauld (secretary to) letter to J. Anthony Denney, 1935 July 8; Courtauld, Samuel, 1876-1947; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 26 x 21 cm (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Courtauld's secretary thanks Denney on behalf of his employer for the invitation to officiate at the opening of the exhibition of the Royal College of Art Sketch Club but declines the offer.
  Letterhead: "12, North Audley Street, W.1 Mayfair 4517"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Courtauld, Samuel, 1876-1947 -- Correspondence; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to Samuel Courtauld, 1935? July 5; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (2 pages): autograph letter; 26 x 20 cm (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Denney informs Courtauld of the upcoming exhibition, asks him to officiate the opening, and notes that "your patronage" would have "such great importance to the students and the college."
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Courtauld, Samuel, 1876-1947 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to W. Reid Dick, 1935 July 6; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 27 x 21 cm (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Denney informs Dick of the upcoming exhibition, and recalls his awarding of the 3 guinea prize for sculpture the previous year. He asks that Dick again award the prize.
  Letterhead: "Royal College of Art Sketch Club, Royal College of Art, South Kensington, S.W.7."
  Correspondence; Sculpture, British; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Dick, William Reid, 1879-1961 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to Randolph Schwabe, 1935? July 6; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter; 26 x 20 cm (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Denney informs Schwabe of the upcoming exhibit and recalls Schwabe's previous giving a prize for "a drawing of 'a modern shaped figure [?].'" Denney asks that Schwabe continue his support.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Schwabe, Randolph, 1885-1948 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to Hubert L. Wellington, 1935? July 6; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (2 pages): autograph letter; 26 x 20 cm (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Denney informs Wellington of the upcoming exhibit and reminds him of his previous two guinea prize for a painting. He asks that Wellington continue his support and invites him to the opening of the exhibition.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Wellington, Hubert, 1879- -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to John Gielgud, 1935 July 10; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter; 27 x 21 cm (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Denney thanks Gielgud for his offer of a "Special Prize" and assures him that "the Committee undertakes to see that sufficient entries are made by this years students," though they will notify him if the number is too small.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to William G. Simmonds, 1935 July 16; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (2 pages): autograph letter, signed; 27 x 21 cm (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Denney mentions the upcoming exhibition, and thanks Simmonds for his past awarding of "a Special Prize of a guinea for the best set of notebook drawings." He asks that Simmonds continue his support for the Club. The letter also contains a large amount of marginalia, including rough text thanking an unnamed individual for agreeing to open the exhibition (probably Kenneth Clark).
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Simmonds, W. G. (William George), 1876-1968 -- Correspondence; Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983
- J. Anthony Denney letter to Augustus John, 1935 October 10; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 29 x 22 cm (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Denney informs John of the upcoming Sketch Club exhibition and requests that he serve as adjudicator for the Etching Section.
  Letterhead: "Royal College of Art Students' Group, Royal College of Art, South Kensington, S.W.7."; added above in writing: "late - Royal College of Art Sketch Club"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; John, Augustus, 1878-1961 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to E.C. Gregory, 1935 October 14; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter; 29 x 22 cm (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Denney thanks Gregory for offering a prize of five guineas for the exhibition on behalf of the committee, and invites him to the opening, which will be officiated by Kenneth Clarke. The final paragraph is crossed out.
  Letterhead: "Royal College of Art Students' Group, Royal College of Art, South Kensington, S.W.7."
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959 -- Correspondence; Clark, Kenneth, 1903-1983
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to Herbert Read, 1935 November 12; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 29 x 22 cm (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Denney informs Read of when the judging of entries into the exhibition will occur, and asks whether these times work for Read and what time they might expect him.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Read, Herbert, 1893-1968 -- Correspondence
- J. Anthony Denney draft letter to P. Wyndham Lewis, 1935 November; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990; 1 sheet (2 pages): autograph letter; 29 x 22 cm (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Denney asks if Lewis might write a forward to the catalogue for the exhibition, or if he might use Lewis's speech from a previous year for that purpose.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Lewis, Wyndham, 1882-1957 -- Correspondence
- W. Reid Dick letter to Frank B. Mason, 1934 July 10; Dick, William Reid, 1879-1961; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 18 x 14 cm (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Reid asks Mason to discuss in person what he would want for the Sketch Club; he admits he is "rather in the dark as to what is normal in the way of prizes for the Sketch Club."
  Letterhead: 31, Grove End Road, St John's Wood, N.W.8., Tel. Maida Vale 4197
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Dick, William Reid, 1879-1961 -- Correspondence; Mason, Frank B. -- Correspondence
- Campbell Dodgson letter to Evelyn Hunt, 1937 November 28; Dodgson, Campbell, 1867-1948; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 12 x 18 cm (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Dodgson says he will do what Hunt asked; he only needs to know "just what I have to do, and when."
  Letterhead: "Burlington Fine Arts Club, 17 Savile Row, London, W.1., Telephone Regent 6432"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Dodgson, Campbell, 1867-1948 -- Correspondence; Hunt, Evelyn Janet, 1914-2001 -- Correspondence
- J.H. Evans letter to J. Anthony Denney (?), 1935 November 18; Evans, J. H.; 1 sheet (2 pages): autograph letter, signed; 18 x 12 cm (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Evans asks the price of "the line engraving by B. Morray Williams [later Árnason] entitled Time Arrested--and of her wood engraving of Thistledown." Prices--319 and 355, respectively--are listed by each work, and written in the upper left corner, in a different ink and hand. An address is written on the back, in the same hand as the prices (possibly J. Anthony Denney).
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Evans, J. H. -- Correspondence; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence; Árnason, Barbara, 1911-1975
- H. Vernon Gardner letter to Frank B. Mason, 1934 October 8; Gardner, H. Vernon; 1 sheet (1 page): autograph letter, signed; 17 x 13 cm (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Gardner says he would be pleased to judge Nugent Monck's prize for him, and discusses when he would be available to do so. In a different hand, in the bottom corner, it reads: "Later Nugent Monck withheld his prize because nobody had a design for it. And quite rightly too!"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Gardner, H. Vernon -- Correspondence; Mason, Frank B. -- Correspondence; Monck, Walter Nugent Bligh, 1878-1958
- John Gielgud letter to Frank B. Mason, 1934? July 10; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 18 x 12 cm (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Gielgud says he would be happy to offer a prize for "Theatrical Design,", but says "it is impossible for me to promise to judge, as I have no idea what work I shall be doing in the autumn" though "I shall, hope, however, to be able to see the designs this time, if I am in London and not working day and night!" Written below, in another hand, is "Good man, this Gielgud!"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000 -- Correspondence; Mason, Frank B. -- Correspondence
- John Gielgud letter to Frank B. Mason, 1934 July 13; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 18 x 12 cm (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Gielgud encloses a check for the prize amount and says he would like to attend and give the prize, if he is able. Written below, in a different hand, "judged by Mrs. Gabrielle Enthoven."
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000 -- Correspondence; Mason, Frank B. -- Correspondence; Enthoven, Gabrielle, 1868-1950
- S. Holmes (secretary to John Gielgud) letter to unidentified recipient (probably Margaret Kaye), 1936 November 12; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000; 1 sheet (2 pages): autograph letter, signed; 18 x 12 cm (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Holmes explains that Gielgud cannot make it to the exhibition to judge, but that the Committee might contact Gabrielle Enthoven instead.
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Kaye, Margaret, 1912-2002 -- Correspondence; Gielgud, John, 1904-2000 -- Correspondence; Enthoven, Gabrielle, 1868-1950
- Eric C. Gregory letter to J. Anthony Denney, 1935 October 15; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 26 x 19 cm (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Gregory thanks Denney for the invitation to attend the exhibition, and expresses his sympathy for the work, though regrets he cannot make any definite commitment to attending the show.
  Letterhead: "Percy Lund Humphries & Co LTD, 12 Bedford Square, London WC1"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959 -- Correspondence; Denney, Anthony, 1913-1990 -- Correspondence
- Eric C. Gregory letter to Margaret Kaye, 1936 August 13; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 26 x 18 cm (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Gregory remembers his last prize--"a booklet had to be prepared, with cover and inside, suitable in layout for the boot trade or for travel (or was it for cameras and photography?)"--and thinks about ways to broaden the conditions.
  Letterhead: "Eric C. Gregory, The Country Press, Bradford. Telephone: Bradford 3408"
  Correspondence; Royal College of Art (Great Britain). Sketch Club; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959 -- Correspondence; Kaye, Margaret, 1912-2002 -- Correspondence
- Eric C. Gregory letter to Evelyn Hunt, 1937 October 4; Gregory, Eric, 1887-1959; 1 sheet (1 page): typed letter, signed; 26 x 18 cm (Box 1, Folder 28)